Finding Aid for the Program for Art on Film Records, 1951-1999, undated IA20008
Institutional Records and Archives
- Program for Art on Film and Production Laboratory records, 1971-1999; (bulk 1984-1994); Series I.; 67 Linear Feet; (circa 71 boxes)
  - Art on Film/Film on Art records, 1984-1998; Series I.C.; 25.5 Linear Feet; (29 boxes)
    - Promotional materials, 1986-1998; Series I.C.3; approx. 2.5 linear feet 4 boxes
      - Photographs and related materials:
        - Cordoba multiple photos, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Beauvais photographs, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Beauvais multiple photographs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Anamorphosos multiple photographs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Anamorphosos photographs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Maximilian multiple photographs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Mark Whitney: Leonardo photograph, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - MA photographs, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - MA multiple photographs, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Leonardo multiple photos, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Grand Canal multiple photos, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Grand Canal photographs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Gombrich multiple photographs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Gombrich photos, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Giorgione's multiple photographs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Giorgione's photographs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Fayum multiple photographs, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Fayum photographs, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
        - Cormack/Maben photos, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-88A)
      - Promotional and press materials:
        - Day on the Grand Canal, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
        - Art on Film/Film on Art, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-12)
        - File copies: Promo, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - PAF - PR /Promo, 1989-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - Testimonials, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - Clippings about Production Laboratory, 1987-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - Fan mail, 1993-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - Fan mail #3, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - Fan mail #1, 1986-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - Press coverage, 1986-1987 (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - Press book - add, 1994-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - [Press Coverage: "Fan Mail" for Art on Screen: A Directory of Films and Videos on the Visual Arts (2 copies); Press Releases, etc. (3 copies); Production Lab Photos; miscellaneous press releases], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-91)
        - Press Releases, 1987-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-96B)
  - Art on Screen database and records, 1994-1998; Series I.D.; 0.4 Linear Feet; 0.04 GB; (1 box)
    These records are listed in the order found within the accession.
    Records comprise correspondence, memoranda, notes, database definitions, web page printouts, database printouts, csv and xls copies of the data, and a clipping, dated 1994-1998, created by the Program for Art on Film in the course of developing their website and, in particular, the Art on Screen database and its public interface.
    Most of the films documented in the Art on Screen database were produced between 1970 and 1998, with selective coverage of productions from 1915 to 1969. Each of the roughly 26,000 citations includes a synopsis, credits, country, language, production date, format, and other filmographic data. The last addition to the database was made in 1998. The database includes productions from more than 70 countries. Subjects covered include fine arts (painting, sculpture, drawing), architecture, archaeology, photography, decorative arts, design, costume, crafts, folk arts, and related topics such as aesthetics and creativity. Media formats covered include film, video, videodisc, multimedia, and CD-ROM productions. The database does not provide information about how to locate copies of the productions or where to view them.
    The Art on Screen Database was hosted on Getty.edu from 2006 until the retirement of the database software in 2018. Since the database structure was extremely flat, it was decided to preserve the data as .csv and .xls files. Interested researchers may access the preserved data files through the link in the inventory below.
    - Art on Screen Database files and screen capture of the gateway webpage used to provide access from 2006 to 2018, 1998
    - Art on Film online, UNET / J. Monaco, 1997 (Box 2008.IA.08)
    - Art on Film online, planning, 1997 (Box 2008.IA.08)
    - Website, 1997-1998 (Box 2008.IA.08)
    - Database definitions, 1998 (Box 2008.IA.08)
    - Database product description (Art on Film), [1997-1998] (Box 2008.IA.08)
    - Data conversion, information and issues, 1994-1996 (Box 2008.IA.08)
  - Art on Screen and Architecture on Screen symposia, 1992-1999; Series I.E.; 6.25 Linear Feet; (6 boxes)
    These records are listed in the order found within the original accession, and by project.
    Records contain correspondence, newsletters, forms, financial documents, published materials, clippings, photographs, programs and brochures describing two projects of the Program for Art on Film, Art on Screen (1992, 1995) and Architecture on Screen (1997-1999). Art on Screen and Architecture on Screen were two symposia organized by the Program in the later years of its existence, and which also resulted in two publications, Art on Screen and Architecture on Screen. The records are primarily concerned with the symposia.
    For information on Art on Screen and Architecture on Screen publications, see Series IB. Publications and publication information.
    - Art on Screen:
      - [Participant folders/handouts for Art on Screen: Film and Video in Museums (3 samples); The Independent: On Location (July 1992) (5 copies)] (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - [Art on Screen miscellaneous materials], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-124)
        [Art on Screen CD-ROM info; Cover photo for Photo book; Art on Screen CD-ROM request for proposal]
      - [Art on Screen transcripts], 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
        [Seminar: Art on Screen, September 13, 1989, Transcript Part I (2 copies); Seminar: Art on Screen, September 13, 1989, Transcript Part II (2 copies).]
    - Architecture on Screen information:
      - Arch '98 NC's [Nadine Covert] file, 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Labels/Lists, 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Arch '98 Masters, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen '98 Survey Forms/Mailing List, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen '98 Thank You Letters/Follow Up, 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen '98 Kudos/Fan Mail, 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Arch '98 Send info, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Advisors/Planning Committee (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Brooklyn Museum of Art, 1997-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Films, 1997-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Films: Confirmations, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Fiscal: Budget/Expenses (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Fundraising/Development (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Arch '98: Fundraising/Dev. C. Madden, Consultant, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen '98 One-Sheet, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen '98 Permission to Show/Right to Tour Forms, 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Pratt Institute, 1997-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Printing/Mailing, 1997-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Publicity/Promotion (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Arch '98: Press materials for films shown at Arch '98 Fest, 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Untitled Folder [press clippings], 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Arch 98: Festival Photos, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Photos, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Press Lists, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen '98 Speakers/Presenters, 1997-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Releases: Arch '98, 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Sponsors/Patrons, 1995-1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Architecture on Screen 1997 Tribute/Reception, 1997-1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Cohen Bros. Program, October 16, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
      - Untitled folder [Architecture on Screen '98 pamphlet], 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
    - Architecture on Screen press materials:
      - [Architecture on Screen press-related materials], 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-104)
        [The Lighthouse Inc. event planning materials folder; The New Press catalog; DuArt Film and Video information; The New Press information; press photos for screened films; miscellaneous information; National Gallery of Art film calendar 1998 (multiple copies); Time Out New York, Jan 29-Feb 5 1998; copies of clippings; Brooklyn Museum of Art Newsletter January-February 1998 (3 copies); Voice Choices (Village Voice, January 28-February 3, 1998); Boston Museum of Fine Arts Film Calendar, January/February 1998]
      - [Architecture on Screen, Art on Screen press and press-related materials], 1994; 1997-1998; [Architecture on Screen '98 pamphlets (multiple copies); Architecture on Screen '98 programs (multiple copies); Architecture on Screen '98 press packets (mutliple copies); Architecture on Screen '98 seating charts; Architecture on Screen '98 festival photos; Critical Inventory Update; Art on Screen Close-Ups, Fall/Winter 1994] (Box 2004.IA.14-122)
      - Untitled folder [Architecture on Screen '98 program mockup], 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-122)
      - Untitled folder [Architecture on Screen '98 information, solicitation letters, press releases], 1998 (Box 2004.IA.14-122)
      - Untitled folder [press releases, posters, Cohen Brothers film], 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-122)
      - Architecture on Screen '98 Touring Program, 1997-1999 (Box 2004.IA.14-122)
  - Interviews, 1987-1992; Series I.F.; 6.5 Linear Feet; (7 boxes)
    Records consist of audiocassettes and transcripts of interviews conducted by Program for Art on Film personnel, 1987-1992. Interviewees included art historians, artists and filmmakers. The majority of the transcripts exist in both unedited and edited versions. Also included are transcripts of focus group interviews.
    - Audiocassettes:
      - [Tapes of interviews with art historians, artists and filmmakers], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-85A)
      - [Tapes of interviews with art historians, artists and filmmakers; focus group transcripts], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-85B)
      - [Tapes of interviews with art historians, artists and filmmakers; focus group transcripts], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-85C)
    - Production Lab transcripts of interviews with filmmakers:
      - Janet Sternburg, 1987-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Janet Sternburg, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Excerpts from Interviews (J. Sternburg), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Transcription Services, 1988-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Art on Film/Film on Art M. Camerini Interviews, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Edited Bergdoll/Descendre [empty folder], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Bergdoll/Descendre, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Brilliant Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - J.J. Brody Edited Interview, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - J.J. Brody Unedited Interview, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Cardinal Interview, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Edited Cormack, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Cormack, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Cran Interview, 1988; 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Edited Cran Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Edited Dodds, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Dodds, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Gombrich Edited Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Gombrich Unedited Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Gould Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Edited Gould Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Greenberg Interview, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Edited Greenberg Interview, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Haas Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Edited Haas Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Hockney Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Edited Hockney Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Iimura Edited Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Iimura Unedited Interview, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Isozaki Edited Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Isozaki Unedited Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Edited Maben, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92A)
      - Unedited Maben, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Marle Edited Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Marle Edited Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Edited McMullen, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Unedited McMullen, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Unedited Murray Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Edited Murray Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Carlo Pedretti Edited, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Carlo Pedretti Unedited, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Unedited Pinto Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Edited Pinto Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Quay Interview, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Unedited Rogers/Shaff Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Edited Rogers/Shaff Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Unedited Rosen/Simon Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Edited Rosen/Simon Interview, 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Edited Syddall and Stacey, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Unedited Syddall and Stacey, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Anita Thacher Edited Interview, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Anita Thacher Unedited Interview, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Edited Velez, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Unedited Velez, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Mark Whitney Edited Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Mark Whitney Unedited Interview, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Edited Wilson, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Unedited Wilson?, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - Columbia University/Murray, Brilliant and Simon, 3/2/89, March 2, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-92B)
      - [Transcripts of interviews with filmmakers], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-126A)
        [Possible duplicates.]
      - [Transcripts of interviews with filmmakers], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-126B)
  - Conferences, seminars and workshops, 1974-1997; Series I.G.; 7.3 Linear Feet; (8 boxes)
    Records include surveys, press releases, clippings, correspondence, letters, reports, photographs, and printed materials, 1974, 1979-1997, regarding conferences, workshops, and educational outreach activities organized, hosted, or undertaken by the Program for Art on Film and the Production Laboratory. One of the earliest conferences, "Art on Film," was held at the Metropolitan Museum of Art and the records document the planning activities for the conference. Education and outreach activities, such as participation in university courses, are documented in the records, as are symposia and screenings held at or with the Louvre and other museums, New York Women in Film, College Art Association and other professional organizations. Also included in the records are documents describing the planning of a seminar organized by the Production Laboratory in 1989 with filmmakers Adams and Goldbard.
    - Museum workshops, surveys, planning documents:
      - Commissioning Films about Art/MMA Museum workshop, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - MMA Workshop, Films, 1990-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - MMA Workshop, Faculty/Registrants, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - MMA Workshop Handout Material, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - MMA Wkshp, Session Notes, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - MMA Museum Workshop, Evaluations/Follow-up Reports, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - MMA Wkshp, Planning: Schedules, March 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Museum Workshop Prototype, April 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Sample Production Contracts, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Houston: Workshop, Planning, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Museum survey, 1986-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Media Center for Children, surveys, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Abrams: AV survey, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Sample surveys, 1974; 1982 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Press coverage: originals, 1992; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Press release originals, 1992-1994; 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Press clippings, 1991; 1993-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Fundraising, 1997 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Untitled folder, 1990-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
        [Press clippings and letters of support.]
      - Letters of support: originals, 1995-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - DOCS: copies of, 1993-1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Business plan, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - PAF development: brainstorming/meetings, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - History Met film, 1941; undated (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
      - Hockney/Haas: press, 1986; 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-82)
    - Education/Outreach Activities:
      - The Arts and Media (Conferences, etc.), 1979-1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Cine: City Conference, 3/94, 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Interdisciplinary Arts Programs, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Art and Film/Media: Courses, 1990; 1991,; 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - S. Delson Class at NYU (1995) (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Center for History in the Media Education Programs: GWU, 1996 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - R. Connor: Hunter College class: Video on Art and Artists, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Film Department: NYU, 1989-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Education Inquiries, 1990-1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Ideas: Education/Outreach, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Outreach Activities Miscellaneous, 1989-1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Lab Education and Outreach Projects, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - University Outreach, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Art L.A., 1987-1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Museums and Film/Video, 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Touchstone Survey Forms, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Touchstone Survey, 1984-1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - 1986 Touchstone Update (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - TS Survey Spring 1986, Letters Rec'd etc. (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Touchstone: Letters rec'd, 1984 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Touchstone Survey Mailing Lists, 1984; 1988 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Touchstone Lists, 1985-1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
      - Touchstone Report (update), 1985 (Box 2004.IA.14-95)
    - Conference, film screenings:
      - [Art History and Film Symposium; Sound and Image conference information], 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
        [Conference attendees folders, Art History and Film Symposium, November 14, 1991 (4 copies); Art History and Film: Starting from the Art, Symposium Report, 1991 (2 copies); contact sheets and negatives, Sound and Image conference; Sound & Images Conference Report, 1991 (2 copies); negatives and photos, Art History and Film symposium.]
      - University of Southern California: Sound and Images Reports, 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-124)
      - Art History and Film Symposium: Report (PAF), undated (Box 2004.IA.14-94)
      - [Information about excerpts from two educational events produced by Program for Art on Film], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - CAA 1990 "Beyond Slides" video taping/dvd-video, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - CAA 1990 "Beyond Slides" Session Rejected Proposals, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Louvre Presentation of PAF Films, 6/90, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - NYWIF Panel: Art on Film, 11-29-90, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Creative Solutions: April 7th Panel, 1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - CAA 1990 "Beyond Slides" Research and Planning, 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - CAA 1990 "Beyond Slides" Session (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - R. Brilliant lecture at Col. U., 2/91, February 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Princeton Seminar, 2/91, February 1991 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - LACMA Screening (aborted plans) (1991) (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - National Gallery screening Dr. Erika Langmuir Information, 6/92, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - NFT (Nat'l Film Theatre) 6/92, London Screening, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Lists, London, 6/92, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - London: Films (ship/cust), 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - London: Follow-up Correspond., 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - London: Printed Materials, 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Untitled folder [Quotes from British teams of filmmakers and art experts, Program for Art on Film productions], undated (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - NYFC Program, Sept 19, 1989, "Film and Video at the Metropolitan", September 19, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - NYF/VC Meeting 12/93, December 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - WIF Brown Bag Lunch 9/92, September 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - SAH April 1994 Society of Architectural Historians (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - ARLIS 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - NYWIF April 14, 1993 panel (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - ARLIS presentation 2/86, February 1986 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - SAH Newsletter Articles 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Arch. on Screen at the Met, 2/94, February 1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - FIFARC 1993/94, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Architecture: Press Contacts, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Wash. Area Arch. Group 9/93, September 1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Chicago Inst. for Arch. and Urb, undated (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Wexner Ctr. Arch. Screening 1/94, 1993-1994 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - ILT Wkshp, 4-21-95, April 21, 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Milia conference (Cannes, France), 1994-1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-41)
      - Association Télévision et Culture (Paris), September 1995 (Box 2004.IA.14-41)
      - Art on Film Festival: Proposal (not produced), 1992 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - Art on Film Festival: Notes, 1992-1993 (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
      - The Visual Arts in Prime Time (conference planning, 1988) (Box 2004.IA.14-106)
    - [PAF Seminar and Workshop], 1989-1990 (Box 2004.IA.14-110)
      [In binders that need rehousing: Creative Solutions: The Challenge of Art on Film, 4/7/90; Creative Solutions: The Challenge of Art on Film; Sept. 13, 1989 Seminar papers; Art on Screen Seminar, Transcript Part II, Adams & Goldberg [Goldbard], 1989; Art on Screen Seminar, Transcript Part II, Adams & Goldbard, 1989; MMA (NYC) Museum Workshop Transcript; Art on Film Selected Bibliography, Susan Logan, 1985; Women in Film Panel Discussion "Art on Film" 11/29/90; Transcripts of Symposia, CAA 2/90, MMA 4/90; Nuts & Bolts Prod. Seminar, R. Bordiga.]
    - Production Lab seminars (Adams and Goldbard, 9/89):
      - Quotes paper, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - History and genres paper, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - Mailing: final version, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - Originals for xeroxing, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - Background paper: Art on Screen, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - Participant lists, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - Planning, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - Consultants, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - Budget and billing, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - Participants' comments to P.L. films, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
      - Outline/Questions/Commissioning, 1989 (Box 2004.IA.14-119)
  - Legal documents, 1985-1999; Series I.H.; 4.17 Linear Feet; (4 boxes)